Help us improve your Mozilla experience
---------------------------------------

In addition to Cookies necessary for this site to function, we’d like your permission to set some additional Cookies to better understand your browsing needs and improve your experience. Rest assured — we value your privacy.

Accept All Additional Cookies Reject All Additional Cookies [Cookie settings](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/privacy/websites/cookie-settings/)

Menu

**Firefox is [no longer supported](https://support.mozilla.org/kb/firefox-users-windows-7-8-and-81-moving-extended-support) on Windows 8.1 and below.**

Please download Firefox ESR (Extended Support Release) to use Firefox.

**Firefox is [no longer supported](https://support.mozilla.org/kb/firefox-users-macos-1012-1013-1014-moving-to-extended-support) on macOS 10.14 and below.**

Please download Firefox ESR (Extended Support Release) to use Firefox.

    Close Firefox Browsers menu
    
    * [
        
        #### Firefox for Desktop
        
        Get the not-for-profit-backed browser on Windows, Mac or Linux.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/new/)
        
    * [
        
        #### Firefox for Android
        
        Get the customizable mobile browser for Android smartphones.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/browsers/mobile/android/)
        
    * [
        
        #### Firefox for iOS
        
        Get the mobile browser for your iPhone or iPad.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/browsers/mobile/ios/)
        
    * [
        
        #### Firefox Focus
        
        Simply private mobile browsing.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/browsers/mobile/focus/)
        
    * [#### Firefox Blog
        
        Read about new Firefox features and ways to stay safe online.](https://blog.mozilla.org/firefox/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=firefox)
        
    * [#### Release Notes
        
        Get the details on the latest Firefox updates.](https://www.mozilla.org/firefox/132.0.2/releasenotes/)

    Close Products menu
    
    * [
        
        #### Mozilla Monitor
        
        See if your email has appeared in a company’s data breach.](https://monitor.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=products)
        
    * [#### Facebook Container
        
        Help prevent Facebook from collecting your data outside their site.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/facebookcontainer/)
        
    * [
        
        #### Pocket
        
        Save and discover the best stories from across the web.](https://getpocket.com/firefox_learnmore/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=products)
        
    * [
        
        #### Mozilla VPN
        
        Get protection beyond your browser, on all your devices.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/products/vpn/)
        
    * [
        
        #### Firefox Relay
        
        Sign up for new accounts without handing over your email address.](https://relay.firefox.com/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=products)
        
    * [
        
        #### MDN Plus
        
        New features and tools for a customized MDN experience](https://developer.mozilla.org/plus?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=products)
        
    * [
        
        #### Fakespot
        
        Use AI to detect fake reviews and scams](https://fakespot.com/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=products)

    Close Who We Are menu
    
    * [#### Mozilla Manifesto
        
        Learn about the values and principles that guide our mission.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/about/manifesto/)
        
    * [#### Mozilla Foundation
        
        Meet the not-for-profit behind Firefox that stands for a better web.](https://foundation.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=who-we-are)
        
    * [#### Leadership
        
        Meet the team that’s building technology for a better internet.](https://www.mozilla.org/about/leadership/)
        
    * [#### Get involved
        
        Join the fight for a healthy internet.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/contribute/)
        
    * [#### Careers
        
        Work for a mission-driven organization that makes people-first products.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/careers/)
        
    * [#### Mozilla Blog
        
        Learn about Mozilla and the issues that matter to us.](https://blog.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=who-we-are)
        
    * [#### Impact
        
        Find out how we’re making the internet more inclusive and sustainable](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/impact/)

    Close Innovation menu
    
    * [
        
        #### Firefox Developer Edition
        
        Get the Firefox browser built just for developers.](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/developer/)
        
    * [
        
        #### MDN Web Docs
        
        Check out the home for web developer resources.](https://developer.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=innovation)
        
    * [
        
        #### Mozilla Innovation Projects
        
        Discover ways to bring bright ideas to life.](https://future.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=innovation)
        
    * [
        
        #### Common Voice
        
        Donate your voice so the future of the web can hear everyone.](https://commonvoice.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=nav&utm_content=innovation)

Mozilla Privacy Policy
======================

September 9, 2020

What do we mean by "personal information?"
------------------------------------------

For us, "personal information" means information which either directly identifies you (like your name, email address, or billing information) or can be reasonably linked or combined to identify you (like an account identification number or IP address). We’ll always tell you what personal information we’re collecting from you. See each product’s Privacy Notice for specific details.

Any information that falls outside of this is "non-personal information."

If we store your personal information with information that is non-personal, we will consider the combination as personal information. If we remove all personal information from a set of data then the remaining is non-personal information.

How do we learn information about you?
--------------------------------------

We learn information about you when:

* you give it to us directly (e.g., when you choose to send us crash reports);
* we collect it automatically through our products and services (e.g., when your Firefox browser checks with us to see if it is up to date);
* someone else tells us information about you (e.g., when Thunderbird works with your email providers to set up your account); or
* when we try and understand more about you based on information you've given to us (e.g., when we use your IP address to customize language for some of our services).

What do we do with your information once we have it?
----------------------------------------------------

When you give us information, we will use it in the ways for which you've given us permission. Generally, we use your information to help us provide and improve our products and services for you.

For users in the EU, EEA, Switzerland, and California: see [here](https://support.mozilla.org/kb/information-eu-eea-and-swiss-users) for more information.

When do we share your information with others?
----------------------------------------------

* When we have asked and received your permission to share it.
* For processing or providing products and services to you, but only if those entities receiving your information are contractually obligated to handle the data in ways that are approved by Mozilla.
* When we are fulfilling our [mission of being open](https://www.mozilla.org/about/manifesto/). We sometimes release information to make our products better and foster an open web, but when we do so, we will remove your personal information and try to disclose it in a way that minimizes the risk of you being re-identified.
* When the law requires it. We follow the law whenever we receive requests about you from a government or related to a lawsuit. We'll notify you when we're asked to hand over your personal information in this way unless we're legally prohibited from doing so. When we receive requests like this, we'll only release your personal information if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. Nothing in this policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party's request to disclose your information.
* When we believe it is necessary to prevent harm to you or someone else. We will only share your information in this way if we have a good faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of you, our other users, Mozilla or the public.
* If our organizational structure or status changes (if we undergo a restructuring, are acquired, or go bankrupt) we may pass your information to a successor or affiliate.

How do we store and protect your personal information?
------------------------------------------------------

We are committed to protecting your personal information once we have it. We implement physical, business and technical security measures. Despite our efforts, if we learn of a security breach, we'll notify you so that you can take appropriate protective steps.

We also don't want your personal information for any longer than we need it, so we only keep it long enough to do what we collected it for. Once we don't need it, we take steps to destroy it unless we are required by law to keep it longer.

What if we change this privacy policy or any of our privacy notices?
--------------------------------------------------------------------

We may need to change this policy and our notices. The updates will be posted online. If the changes are substantive, we will announce the update through Mozilla's usual channels for such announcements such as blog posts and forums. Your continued use of the product or service after the effective date of such changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes. To make your review more convenient, we will post an effective date at the top of the page.

#### Contact Mozilla

If you want to make a correction to your information, or you have any questions about our privacy policies, please get in touch with:

Mozilla Corporation  
Attn: Mozilla - Privacy  
149 New Montgomery St, 4th Floor,  
San Francisco, CA 94105  
USA  

[See here for Data Subject Access Requests.](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/1350748f-7139-405c-8188-22740b3b5587/4ba08202-2ede-4934-a89e-f0b0870f95f0) If you are under 13, we don’t want your personal information, and you must not provide it to us. If you are a parent and believe that your child who is under 13 has provided us with personal information, please contact us to have your child’s information removed.

For product support requests, please [visit our forums](https://support.mozilla.org/).

Menu
----

* Mozilla Privacy

---------------------------------------------------------

Data Privacy Principles
-----------------------

Mozilla’s [Data Privacy Principles](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/privacy/principles/) inspire our practices that respect and protect people who use the internet. Learn how these principles shape Firefox and all of our products in this [FAQ](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/privacy/faq/)

Transparency Report
-------------------

As an open source project, transparency and openness are an essential part of Mozilla’s founding principles. Our codebases are open and auditable. Our development work is open. Our bi-annual [Transparency Report](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/about/policy/transparency/) also demonstrates our commitment to these principles.

Get Involved
------------

To review and comment on proposed changes to our privacy policies, [subscribe to Mozilla’s governance group](https://groups.google.com/a/mozilla.org/g/governance/).

Read more about our ongoing privacy and security public policy work on [Mozilla’s Open Policy and Advocacy Blog](https://blog.mozilla.org/privacy/).

-------------------------------------------------------------------

Company
-------

Resources
---------

Support
-------

Developers
----------

Follow @Mozilla
---------------

Follow @Firefox
---------------

[Language](https://www.mozilla.org/locales/) Language Čeština Deutsch English Español (de España) Français magyar Bahasa Indonesia Italiano 日本語 Nederlands Polski Português (do Brasil) Русский 中文 (简体) Go

Visit [Mozilla Corporation’s](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/) not-for-profit parent, the [Mozilla Foundation](https://foundation.mozilla.org/?utm_source=www.mozilla.org&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=footer).  
Portions of this content are ©1998–2024 by individual mozilla.org contributors. Content available under a [Creative Commons license](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/foundation/licensing/website-content/).
